Did you know that the newest trend are silicone catsuits?
And I've already shown some on my channel but today I have...
Oh it's already heavy!
I have a special one. It is for women's sizes.
It's smaller and it is shaped for boobs.
And I'm going to show you this one from Futura X.
They do not only have catsuits but also something like this mask.
I'm going to show you more of them later on.
Now let's unpack this.
All right, it's like one and I'm going to unroll it.
There we go.
I have to wait it because
I can do weight training with it basically.
You can already see that the booty is pre-shaped and 3D,
which is going to be really cool.
And I'm going to change.
all right here I am I squeezed into it it is a neck entry so yes you have to
squeeze through the neck there are no zippers though Futura X says on their
homepage if you want to have a zipper option you should write them an email so
do so if you're really interested in that and what should I say it looks
fantastic I mean it's just it's just great I can't I can't find any flaws
it's really just hugging my my figure and enhancing it and making it even
better I have already shown you that the booty was like pre molded so it's really
giving a nice butt shape with the boobs the same so you don't need any inlays as
you would need with latex to form your figure you don't need any I don't know
push-up bras or something the suit itself has a figure and it gives you its
figure and you can wear it and just look great I also love the collarbones that
are molded and basically 3d modeled because they make it just nice look and
I love collarbones anyway. It was a bit harder to squeeze into it because it's not too big. So it
is really for small size for women. You can order it in two different sizes. And what can I say?
It's just still like stretchy. I can still move around and move every part of my body.
so it's really comfortable it's basically a matte look I've just taken a washcloth to wipe it down
and let it dry but of course I can shine it up this is the shine out that Futura extends with it
and recommends to use so I am going to use it and try to shine the suit up
I think it works
I shined it up and considering two looks of course shining it up is more work and you will
always find a piece of lint sticking to it because um yeah hair and dust likes to stick
to silicone apparently I had to learn that too so it's always handy to have a white cloth to wipe
it off and yeah that's the shiny look I like it too though I have to say I also like the matte
look silicone is a great alternative if you have a latex allergy for example and you want to wear
a suit or something like this too I already got the feedback that people with latex allergies said
yes that's a cool thing so check it out also of course it is heavier than latex I think this is
around about four kilogram it's four millimeter thick so it is simply more than latex if you want
to feel more weight more enclosure more restriction then this might be something for you too and
of course also if you simply want to try something new and like have experience with latex for years
already and say yay that looks great I do have a discount code you can check it out in the
description text and you get some percent off and a small discount if you lose my link down there
and as I already said in comparison to latex it gives you basically a figure that adds to your own
body and does not push it down or makes the booty look flat or something like that because
of the 3D modeling here. So these are the differences to latex. Everyone always asks
how does it feel compared to latex. Well it's a bit more squishy initially and of course it's
thicker so it's as I said heavier more restricting. It is probably more durable the latex
when it comes to destroying it simply because it's 4mm thick.
Something else I received from Fitorix were these gloves.
They are perfect fit to the catsuit.
And I want to show them to you close up first because they have nails.
Pretty cool.
I'm simply going to put this on my hands and put the gloves on.
something else I learned to do it until your
Fingertips because otherwise your fingertips will get stuck in the silicon
And now getting it to 10
Go
Can already feel the vacuum on my fingertips
I feel like I have pores now.
By the way they are also available as pores and with coloured nails.
Alright and now more to shine them up.
So we are going to try and spread it like this.
This is the final look with gloves, they look awesome, I mean they're a bit creepy with
the fingernails but I think that's a really cool look and yeah it's a bit hard to touch
something now but it's all about the look.
Vitorex does not only do gloves and catsuits but they also have a range of silicone masks,
They are also for women and smaller head circumferences.
So if you're into hoods, you should definitely check them out.
I think they're super cute.
I mean, these ears or whatever these are, ears, they're super cute and squishy.
And I also love this design.
There will be another video on my channel in which the masks are going to be featured in the future.
If I'm going to show this to you, you can, for example,
detach the mask of the mask part mask for example and it's a bit more difficult
with the hands of course and here we got some stuff where you can insert a tube
but yeah as I said I'll show this again in another video now it's open I can't close it with a
cloth anyway what do you think of the catsuit and what do you think of the
cloth in the max tell me in the comments check out the description text for the
link to the Futurix webpage and my discount code I had a lot of fun
presenting you this suit and I still love when I look in the mirror how it
looks on me and how well it fits so yeah leave a thumbs up I should make a gif
although I don't even give a thumbs up and leave a comment subscribe to my channel I will see
you in the next video have a nice day bye